Then what happened at this time,
good afternoon Anuj ji, good afternoon
Harshita ji, so see, the recommendation is
bar accommodation on ICICI, now
I am talking about ICICI Lombard
because see, if you look at the pattern here, a
bridge pattern has formed, I
think just a few days ago the stock
made a bottom around 1120, after that
in the five day consultation, ICICI was pressing resistance on the average in 20 team,
but today the 20
average has come in, just a few minutes
ago in this step it is at 22, I have realigned it and taken out
above it,
volume was seen there, so
you have to buy with a stop loss of 11, 11, 39, the
target in ICICI will be 1170 and
here you can also take option trade, the
December ICICI is
standing around 1160,
buy there with a stoppage of 29 rupees
for a target of 60 rupees,
ok ICICI
gives an update  I am here, all the railway
stocks like IRCTC are moving,
special Ricky is showing on your screen at this time
404.40 of this period means last last is
almost 10 sessions at the highest cliff,
Ritz's Hitech is treating at around
4:34 and RVNL in the morning, in fact,
in our description, we had also mentioned it in FERA,
that too will give
directory market rate, doing
good mobile in all the railway stocks, meanwhile its
move and snake is happening at 29883, now
Nifty it is 500 points up, hello Amit Seth ji,
welcome to the program,
tell me your call at this time